Machiavelli! You've told me nothing
I don't already know!
Sun Tzu's The Art of War.
Stewie, those books aren't
for babies. Here. Watch the Teletubbies.
How dare you! That book may hold the key
to my enslaving of all mankind.
Fuzzy.
Tickle.
God. The more I resist, the more intriguing
they become! I can't look away!
Again! Again!
Yes! Yes! Again! Again!
Dear God, please once more!
Sorry, Stewie.
A&E Biography is doing the life
of the other guy from Wham.
I'm free! Free from the spell
of those diabolical Teletubbies!
Thank you. When the world is mine,
your death shall be quick and painless.
"It seems today that all you see
"is violence in movies and sex on TV
"But where are those good,
old-fashioned values
"on which we used to rely?
"Lucky there's a family guy
"Lucky there's a man who'll
positively tell you
"all the things that make us
"laugh 'n' cry
"He's a family guy"
Attention, please.
Tomorrow is softball practice. We have
a lot of work to do for Saturday's game.
Don't forget how badly we were humiliated
last year by Pawtucket Joke and Novelties.
Look at those morons
and their stupid glasses.
Oh, man. I hate those guys.
More than I hate spinach, traffic jams,
and the last few years of M* A*S*H.
When Alan Alda took over
behind the camera...
...and the show
got all dramatic and preachy?
Am I right? Who's with me?
This year we will defeat those Pranksters
with our secret weapon...
...Guillermo.
Bravo!
I hired Guillermo because I believe
he'll be an asset to our company...
...on and off the field.
You have impeccable credentials.
I'm sure I can find a position
for you somewhere.
Back to work, people.
Mr. Weed, I got a great idea for
a new line of TV action figures.
Facts of Life Transformers, huh?
Watch the transformation.
Cute as a button...
...fat as a cow...
...radioactive scorpion.
Watch out, Mrs. Garrett. Here comes Blair.
- I'll consider it.
- He'll consider it!
I got another one where Natalie's one of
those spittin' lizards from Jurassic Park.
Pat, I would like to solve the puzzle.
"Go tuck yourself in. "
You got it.
Well, you were close, Dad.
Yeah. I still can't believe we missed
the phrase, "My hairy aunt. "
Come on, Brian.
I gotta get to softball practice.
Practice? I thought we'd go next door
and welcome our new neighbors.
No. I don't want anything to do
with neighbors.
Last guy who lived next door
borrowed my toaster. Never saw it again.
If that slut wants full custody of the kids,
she's got it.
Peter, they might be very nice people.
"Very nice people. "
Yeah, that's what they always say.
Then you open up the septic tank and...
Skeleton city!
Pervert!
Don't flatter yourself, honey.
I don't have any sweat glands.
Okay, time for batting practice,
my Happy-Go-Lucky Toy Boys.
Guillermo, you're up.
Unfortunately Johnson isn't here
to pitch today. His wife is in labor.
Oh, what? Is the baby coming out of him?
Jeez, I'll pitch.
I don't know what's more questionable,
your pitching arm or Bill Clinton's integrity.
Oh, how hard...
Oh, how hard can it be to pitch?
- Okay. Take your base.
- Somebody call 911.
Tell them he is allergic to penicillin
and white zinfandel!
Idiot! If you don't find a ringer
to replace Guillermo, you're fired!
Man. What'll I do if I get fired?
I'll have to go back to my old job...
...as a Calvin Klein model.
I don't wanna be like everyone else.
But I don't want to be different.
I just want to be.
What was the name
of the bad guy from Tron?
This is gonna drive me nuts!
Moving is never easy on a family.
Well, we are gonna miss
the go-go-go pace of Providence.
But with number two on the way,
Joe thought it was time to move.
And I can't say no to Joe. Ever.
Quahog can be pretty exciting, too.
Last week, someone lost an eye at Bingo.
I-17. Darn it.
I haven't played Bingo in years!
Silence! Ever since you two met,
you've done nothing but wax idiotic!
I must escape this infernal babble!
What a little explorer.
Yes. He's so full of wonder.
To be the Lindbergh baby right about now.
Joe, you have to meet
our new neighbor, Lois Griffin.
It's a pleasure, Lois. Who's the little guy?
This is Stewie.
Honey, say hi to Mr. Swanson.
You will bow to me.
Hi. I'm Meg. I live next door.
I know.
I've admired you in the garden from afar.
- Will you go out with me?
- I'd love to.
Oh, he's gay.
You wish!
Get out of here, you mouth breather!
I'm as good as fired.
Where the hell am I gonna find a guy
as strong as Guillermo?
One time I walked into the locker room,
I swear he was bench-pressing Mr. Weed.
Great. Lois is getting chummy
with the new neighbors.
She wants you to meet them.
She's always making me be social.
Cocktail parties, school functions,
that time we planted trees in Jerusalem.
What? Look, all I'm saying is
put an Israeli guy next to an Arab guy...
...and I can't tell the difference.
- You must be Peter. Joe Swanson.
- Yeah, yeah. Nice to meet you, Phil.
You got a neighbor
on the other side of your house, too.
So, don't think you always have to bug me.
I'll keep that in mind. Say, do you have
a screwdriver I can borrow?
Man, you neighbors are like viruses.
Starts with a screwdriver.
Before you know it,
you're using my supermarket...
...my dry cleaner, and even my postman.
Can you believe that guy?
"Do you have a screwdriver I can borrow?"
What an ass.
- Did you find a replacement for the team?
- No. Believe me, I've been looking.
Hideo-san would be honored to play
for your team.
But he wishes to know
what compensation you offer.
Me love you long time.
Gosh, I'd like to help.
But I've gotta go out in the hall...
...and chew on my ass for five minutes.
Peter, I invited Joe and Bonnie
to your game on Saturday.
Lois, I don't want those people there.
See, this is why I ask you
to submit everything to me in writing first.
Bonnie told me Joe is a big baseball fan.
He played in college.
He did?
Welcome to the neighborhood.
Hiya, Joe.
- Peter!
- Don't get up.
This is a surprise.
I kinda thought you didn't like me.
What? Because of what I said
this afternoon. No.
See I have that disease
where stuff pops out of your mouth.
Go to hell! Whoops. See what I mean?
I'm so sorry.
I thought maybe I crossed the line
when I asked to borrow a screwdriver.
Are you kidding?
You can borrow whatever you want.
Great. Say, you don't happen
to have any picture wire, do you?
Picture wire? You son of a bitch.
Son of a bitch! Son of a bitch!
There it goes again.
I don't want to impose.
No problem. That's what neighbors do.
You know what else they do?
They play on their neighbor's company
softball team like this Saturday.
What do you say, neighbor?
Sounds fun.
So much fun it should be illegal
like copyright infringement.
See you at the game, Joe.
- Hey, you want a piece of gum?
- Thanks.
- That was joke gum.
- What do you mean?
Now you're addicted to heroin.
I'm cold.
Hey, Peter!
It's nice that your family is here.
If your ringer doesn't arrive soon,
you can spend every day with them...
...at home.
He'll be here, Mr. Weed.
You should see this guy in action.
He can hit, he can throw...
Peter!
What's he doing in a wheelchair?
Holy crip, he's a crapple!
Peter, our new secret weapon
is this very attractive paraplegic?
Okay, Joe, you got me.
Rise and shine. Come on.
- Stand and deliver. Get the hell up.
- You're a hoot, Peter.
- Play ball!
- Let's do it!
I swear I didn't know.
Maybe they won't hit a lot of balls to him.
I got shortstop.
The movers tracked grease
all over my carpet.
- I tried everything to get the stain out.
- What about lemon juice?
- What about club soda?
- What about shutting the hell up?
Isn't baseball great?
They say baseball's the national pastime.
I can't taste salt.
Crap! Don't hit it to Joe.
Please don't hit it to Joe!
You're out!
All right, Joe!
Way to earn that parking space!
All right!
Did you see that?
That's my Joe!
What the deuce?
Half man, half machine.
Why with that technology,
I could escape these wretched harridans!
Go, cyborg!
It all rests on that man's broad,
rippling shoulders!
All right, Joe! Run!
All right, Joe! Come on! Yeah!
Hurry! Joe!
All right! Yes, vamos!
Let's hear it for Joe!
Yeah, let's hear it for the guy
who found Joe!
Okay.
That's finger suckin' good, huh?
It's an old policemen's recipe.
Eat up, everyone. Tonight my wife won't
be the only one enjoying a pig in a blanket.
Joe, you're so funny.
They love that one down at the Precinct.
This sucks, Brian.
Joe is stealing my thunder.
Hey, everybody! Time to limbo!
- Face it. He's the life of the party.
- Yeah?
I'll show you who's the life of the party.
Hey, look!
I fell in the pool with my clothes on!
How hilarious is that?
That is so Peter Griffin. Guys?
Guys?
That's my idea.
Peter, come here.
Finally. A little recognition.
Joe has the most wonderful idea.
Hey, I just suggested a line
of handi-capable toys, you know...
...to show kids the fun side
of being physically challenged!
That's what kids want to play with.
Yeah. A Beanie Baby in a bubble.
What about my idea? Come on!
Tootie morphs into a stink bug.
Joe, you're exactly the kind of man
we need at our company.
Peter, make yourself useful.
Go get Joe a drink.
Jeez, first he takes my friends.
Then he takes my job.
But the way I wear my hat...
No, no. He can't take that away from me.
You! How came you
by this metal construct?
- I demand to know who made you!
- Stewie, it's not polite to point.
I'm so sorry.
That's okay, Lois.
He's just curious about the chair.
About 10 years ago I was investigating
a robbery at an orphanage.
It was Christmas Eve
and some presents had been stolen.
Reach for the sky, dirtbag!
All right, pal!
You've stolen your last Christmas.
"You think you have won
You think all is well
"But kiss my green ass
I shall see you in hell!"
Are you Timmy?
Merry Christmas, Timmy.
Enough!
If you won't share your technological
schemata with me peaceably...
...I shall take the information
from you by force!
Wow. Looks like you have a fan.
- Come on. Let's get out of here.
- Peter, you can't leave.
Sorry, I promised the wife and kids I'd...
...take them on a dream vacation
to Hawaii right now. Say aloha, kids.
What are you talking about? We want to
hear more of Mr. Swanson's stories.
He's cool, Dad. He killed a guy.
Well, technically he was killed by the state,
but funny story.
He did curse my name
just before the injection.
Peter, what's the matter with you?
Why are you guys making such a big deal
over Joe?
You don't admire wheelchair people.
You're supposed to feel sorry for them.
When did it become okay
to be handicapped?
Don't talk like that!
He's a remarkable man
and the rest of your family adores him!
Fine. Then why don't you all marry him?
And if he's so remarkable,
let's see him do this.
Hey, look at me. I'm walking.
I'm a remarkable man.
Well, look who finally came home.
I thought you were gonna spend
all night at Joe's.
I could've. That man has got magic fingers.
He found this one spot behind my ear, I...
Forget about it.
I thought my leg was never gonna stop.
I don't believe this.
My whole family worships the ground
that guy can't walk on.
It's not too hard to see why. He's a hero.
He makes the world a better place.
I've done lots of things to help people.
Remember the time I sang to the kids
at the Sunday school?
Yes, you forgot the words.
"Jesus loves me
"He loves me a bunch
"Because He always puts Skippy
"In my lunch"
No. It's not the same thing.
Joe puts himself in real danger every day.
You're right. I'll never be that kind of hero.
Unless I put myself in real danger, too!
For my family's sake!
Why are the pretty ones
always so dumb?
Gang shooting on
Third and Main. Three wounded, one dead.
- Is it me or is rap music just getting lazier?
- No. It's my new police scanner.
This hero thing is gonna be easy
once I find the right crime.
Domestic disturbance...
Boring!
Report of a stabbing in...
All units! A major robbery
is in progress at Quahog Bank and Trust.
Suspects are armed
and extremely dangerous.
- Perfect! Where's Lois and the kids?
- Over at Joe's.
Well, go fetch 'em.
They're about to see a real hero in action.
To the Batcave!
Oh, God! Oh, God! Oh, God!
You thought Joe was something.
You ain't seen nothin' yet.
Peter, what's the big rush?
All right, you guys wait right here.
Daddy's gonna make a little withdrawal.
Give Tammy a round of applause.
This was her first robbery
and she was very brave.
Now before we go...
No, don't go.
Oh, princess, we have to.
I hope you brought
your striped pajamas, boys.
Because there's a five-year sleepover
at the big house. And you're invited.
You'll never take us alive!
Lois and the kids
should be in here to see this.
Yes. It's going very well.
Mom, what do you do when you like a boy
but he doesn't even notice you?
Meg loves Kevin.
Shut up, you big sack of dog vomit!
Meg, you're a sweet, lovely girl.
He'll come around.
Such a mom answer.
Have you tried showing off the goods?
How's that for a mom answer?
Creepy.
I saw some cute dresses down the street.
If nothing else, it'll make you feel better.
Come on, you guys.
If you want to be a hero,
now might be a good time.
This isn't what I was expecting.
I thought being a hero
would be all fun and games.
Sorry, Wonder Woman.
I got three kings. Now let's see your pair.
All right. Robin, what are you looking
at me for? Look at her.
Come on. Let's go.
Oh, perfect.
We got hostages!
Don't try anything funny!
Don't worry, Brian. I got a plan.
Good. I was afraid
you were just gonna improvise.
Actually, I was gonna use
the little girl as a human shield...
...and run like hell.
But improvise, that'll be easier on my back.
Okay, in this improv, Tammy and
the short robber are husband and wife.
Okay. And where are we?
A bar!
A pet store!
Guadalajara, Mexico!
Okay, okay. I heard pet store.
And I'm the gruff but lovable owner.
All right. Begin. Hello, married couple.
I see you found a puppy.
Yeah. His name is Sparky.
Well, before you take Sparky home,
let me check him for worms.
Okay, drop it!
All right, you guys. Let's get out of here.
All right, stand back!
Whoa. Hang on. Sorry, no one can leave.
Listen, the whole reason I saved
you guys today was so I could be a hero.
This wheelchair guy moved in next door
and he can do all these great things and...
Your family idolizes the lousy cripple
and not you?
That's right! How'd you know?
We've all been there.
Cool! The bank is getting jacked!
Officer, my husband's in there!
- Can you tell me if he's okay?
- What's he look like?
He's wearing a white-collared shirt,
kind of big, with glasses.
I got him.
Oh, thank God.
- Take him out.
- No!
Hey, there's my family.
I just want you to know I rob banks...
...because a deaf man stole my job
at the phone company.
So if anyone's gonna bust me,
I'm glad it's you.
But... But I was gonna be a hero.
Nobody's going anywhere!
Joe, it's Peter! He's in trouble!
A failed robbery at
Quahog Bank and Trust...
...has led to a terrifying hostage situation.
That's right. A hostage situation.
- I gotta go.
- I know.
If we want the cops to take us seriously,
we have to waste a hostage. But who?
- Excuse me. Shouldn't that be "whom"?
- Okay, you.
Crap!
This is Police Lieutenant
Joe Swanson. I know we can work this out.
Not him again. I hope this place
isn't wheelchair accessible.
Bonnie, it's Peter.
Don't worry.
Joe's an excellent negotiator.
I was a virgin when we met.
It took him three hours.
I can't believe my dad is in there.
This'll probably scar me
for the rest of my life.
I got a new dress.
Try talking about him.
So do you like music?
Yeah! I played guitar
in a band before we moved.
But it interfered with my studies.
What do you listen to?
You first.
I'm into Garbage, Phish, Blur.
My parents don't like me
listening to that stuff.
But I do anyway because I am not a robot!
I also like Radiohead.
And even though society has turned
its back on you...
...I promise you there are people who care.
And you know what? I'm one of them.
He sure gets it.
Maybe he's right.
We can make a new start.
Come on, guys.
Don't let him sweet talk you like that.
Wait. You can't leave now.
I'm supposed to be the hero. Wait!
Can you let me pistol-whip you
a couple times for the camera?
Stupid robbers with your guns
and your make-out parties.
Excellent!
They detached the human component
from the machine.
Machine, I am your new master
and I order you to go!
Engage!
Blast! Must be some kind of
proprietary command system.
Now on the Russian MiG,
it's next to the altimeter.
There you are.
I can't turn my back on you for a second.
One day I shall unlock the secret
of that device.
And when I do, Mother, victory shall be...
Peter, you had us so worried.
What on earth were you trying to prove?
I'm sorry. Joe is a great guy.
I guess I was just tired of him
being your hero.
Peter, Joe is a hero. But he's not our hero.
- You are.
- Really?
Yeah.
You're always right there on the couch
for us, making us laugh when we're upset.
Changing the channel
when something boring comes on.
Eating the last slice of pizza
so the rest of us don't fight over it.
Yeah, Daddy.
If you hadn't pulled this stunt...
...I wouldn't know
how to manipulate Kevin.
And when the kids at school see us on TV...
...they'll think you're a total psycho.
And I can say, "That psycho is my dad!"
I wouldn't have won silver in Nagano,
had you not driven me...
...to the ice rink every morning at 6:00 a. m.
I guess being a hero isn't always
about saving lives and catching bad guys.
It's also about just being there
for the people you love.
Help!
Someone just stole my purse!
Who cares? I don't even know you.
Thank you for watching «Family Guy» on
www.FOX-fan.ru